I've eaten some pretty strange things.
Good morning. - Good morning.
You were very tired yesterday.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
Today, we have a special treat for you.
Utsunomiya Gyoza (dumplings)
They say the dumplings at this house are delicious.
I'm so happy!
I was so happy, I had green juice coming out of my eyes.
I thought I was going this way.
Game arcade.
There are 5 places to order from when you enter the store!
All you can eat?
All you can eat.
Really?
Yes!
Then let's all order the dumplings we like and eat them right from the entrance.
It's all-you-can-eat.
GO!
There's cheese in it.
I'll have the mentaiko cheese.
I'll have the shrimp-free dumplings.
Shrimp free?
Yuna is going for a drive today.
I'll join you later.
I'm going for a drive!
I told Tochigi to drive, so please wait a bit.
I'd like to order a menchikatsu.
Anything you like.
What do you want?
Anything you want.
It's on the back menu.
It's all on the menu.
It's totally on the back.
You want these three?
The back menu and the number two, please.
Cool! How to order?
That's totally backwards!
I'm so happy because I really like gyoza.
I know.
I'm going to go to the next store!
Thank you very much. Bon appétit.
A gyoza shop in a place like this.
I'm sorry I'm still here.
One salted yuzu dumpling, please.
It's a Meikikan-only item.
That's great!
Thank you very much.
Let's go next time.
There's a gyoza shop here!
Gyoza-men-men!
With seeds!
Crispy bread in it.
I like crispy bread.
One seeded dumpling, please.
Thank you.
I know, Mimin.
Would you like some fried dumplings?
Delicious! Fried dumplings!
Fried gyoza then.
Two, please.
That's a lot of dumplings.
We can finish it.
I can eat all of them!
This is the fifth and last restaurant!
The green onions look delicious!
Negi is delicious!
Negi shio?
I want some green onions.
One negi shio gyoza, please.
I'll have one.
I'm done.
It's amazing, but the quantity is absolutely terrible!
Let's wait in our seats.
Yay!
Thank you for watching!
Lots of things were happening.
Today, the soba arrived and before we ate it...
Seriously?
I didn't hear it, I didn't hear it.
I thought I heard you.
No, you didn't.
It's a lie. We're just going to eat it today.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yay!
My heart's pounding.
I had my doubts since yesterday. I thought they were going to make us have a meal-potato showdown or something.
It sure seems likely.
Wait a minute, it would be bad if I said that.
Well then, everyone, thank you for your hard work on Draft Live Gunma.
Thank you for your hard work.
Bye bye. With Yuna.
Good work, Yuna.
Yuna went with only Yamashiro.
Eh, what do you want?
I want to eat this.
What is it? Fried dumplings?What is it? Fried dumplings?
You're being extremely extravagant.
Yuna has some too.
There's really something aromatic about it.
I feel like I'm missing something.
Want some Yuuna?
Yuna eat?
I'll have some!
I'm so happy.
I'll eat it.
It's so good.
Bon appétit!
It's really good!
I'm so happy.
Wow, it's delicious.
Really?
It's so good, I'm not even gonna buy it.
Are you jealous?
Yes, I am.
It's just a mestero fonga.
You should see this late at night.
Our late-night mestero fonga.
And shrimp pudding.
It's not bad at all.
It's really good.
I'd love to.
Can I ask the manager to come?
Yeah, I want to.
I want to.
We could have dumplings in the morning.
That's true.
Totally doable.
No problem at all.
The morning gyoza era is coming.
It's coming.
Delicious!
Who only ate the cheese?
No, I just poured it out.
Oh, Kees.
That's what you get for roughhousing.
Bell peppers.
Can you put the message here, please?
Roughing it.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I want to do a taste test with this.
Suddenly, it started.
Taste contest!
I was so excited to see the ball star.
I was getting excited.
Ball Star Dumpling
They look like this.
Close your eyes, everyone!
Let's move on.
Think about it.
Okay.
Everyone take one.
It'll go down everyone's throat.
Hinano-san, let's go.
Close your eyes.
Okay, okay.
What if I'm not good at this?
Can the contestant tell what they're feeding him?
I don't know.
Uh-uh.
I wonder.
Let's go, Karu-chan!
Can you eat it by magic?
Can you do that? Angel?
Angel, hold on!
I have no idea what the last three of us are going to eat.
Oh, I know.
I don't know.
I've eaten some pretty strange food.
Oh, yeah.
I wonder what it is.
I don't know.
Okay, okay.
Open your mouth.
Wow!
That's it.
It's over!
So this is what it looks like. What you just ate...
Now I'd like you all to choose one for yourselves.
I think I'll have the Satsuki dumplings.
You're lying.
Kimchi dumplings.
Satsuki dumplings.
Yuzu dumplings.
Shimomono dumplings.
Green perilla dumpling.
Definitely Satsuki dumplings.
There are three Satsuki dumplings.
If you miss this one, you'll be punished.
Wait, wait, wait!
Mai-chan.
I know it's for the penalty game, but...
Final answer, please.
I'll go with "Noshu gyoza" The final answer is...
I Satsuki GyozaI'm Satsuki Dumpling.
You haven't changed.
My gyoza dumplings.
You haven't changed
My shimono gyoza
Green perilla dumplings.
Incorrect answers, please.
Shimotsuki gyoza.
Shimotsuke?
Fashionable.
Miyu...
Try the tea beauty dumpling.
Tasty!
Rinu-san has kimchi dumplings.
Are they pearls?
Who got the wrong answer?
You don't know.
But Karen...
I poured lemon juice on them.
Here they are.
Limo and guise.
I don't know the second half.
Raise your hand if you missed it.
I'm pretty sure it was the lemon.
I don't even know if you can tell it's a lemon.
I didn't say anything amazing.
Later, the cameraman will give us our punishment.
Who got the wrong answer?
Later?
Enjoy the moment.
Bon appétit.
Limo and guise.
I trust fresh and tasty.
Really? Here you go.
I'll have some.
This was so good.
It's good, isn't it?
Can't you tell?
It's not too much to ask for.
It was surprisingly easy to eat.
Limo and guise!
Yay!
So, we're here at Kirash-san today!
Hahahaha!
Everything was so unique, I wanted to develop something new!
I think I can make a dessert instead of dumplings!
Great! Honey cheese.
Honey cheese?
You want to meet someone?
Let's meet!
I think I can be in a lot of different genres.
It's been a while since we've done something this heavenly.
Yes, it has!
Thank you so much!
I know it's a bit of an office terror video for those of you watching.
I really hope you watch it in the middle of the night.
But you guys are welcome to come.
Please come!
He's a good actor.
He looks totally good, and we all
I love it!
Gyopa!
That was fun!
Translation: Gyopa!
Well, thank you very much for today's video!
Thank you very much!
And look forward to the next video!
Bye bye!
That's all for now!
Terran!
Bye bye!
Okay, everyone, Gyopa!
Gyopa!
Bye-bye!